Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Shrouded in Smoke of Gunpowder
Episode 14
Go home
Wolffy, do you remember which rift leads to Green Green Grassland?
Intuition tells me
it should be
this
Wolffy, you’ve chose a wrong way again
The next one must be
Wolffy
Still not right
When will it end?
So hot
Are fur dolls also afraid of heat?
What a strong wind
Sand—
Sandstorm!
Back to the rift
Such a familiar plot
Sorry Wolffy
We can only wait for the sandstorm to disappear before going back.
Let’s go back quickly
rift
where is it
Sandstorms changed the terrain
We can’t just walk around, we have to look carefully.
rift rift
So tired
I’m so thirsty. Where can I find water?
leave the water
water
Xiao Zhou, Xiao Ze,
and Xiao Ju, the super group appears
Feeling so awesome
attack with love
So scary
Surrender and give us your water and food.
impossible
I wanted you to leave safely
Looks like I’m going to punish you well.
they are in danger
I go to help
Weslie
There’s really nothing I can do against you
Do you still want to resist me like this?
Say it again, hand over all the water
Stealing my goods is tantamount to offending
I don’t care who you are, it’s my territory
No one can disobey me
who
let them go
Isn’t it just a little boy and a stuffed toy?
Don’t look down on stuffed toys
Hit my men? I’ll show you what I’m capable of!
Actually fighting with wool
That doll can still talk
are you okay
Are you injured?
Thank you both for your help. We’re fine.
Just our car
Leave the repair issues to me.
fixed
Thanks for your hard work
Come and have a drink
You’re so wasteful
But
How can you drink water with so much sand?
The most precious thing in this Blue Planet world is water. Don’t pick it.
By the way
You go everywhere as transporters
Have you ever seen a purple rift?
Thank you for the water. Let us take our leave now.
Wait
You don’t have water or a vehicle. It’s very dangerous to walk in the desert.
Why not go to the town and get ready before setting off?
Makes sense
Otherwise we will fall in the desert before we can find the rift.
But we don’t know how to get to the town either.
We need to transport supplies back and we’re on the way.
As a thank you, I’ll send you there.
Then we would rather obey than be respectful.
Take them too
Why?
You’ll find out when you go to the town
Be careful
Sorry sorry sorry
this is
Town?
That’s right, we’re going into town
big sale big sale
The new flying saucer will win prizes if you hit it
Out-of-print toys available with water
This is the exchange
Just complete the exchange’s bounty
You can exchange them for corresponding water, food, and other supplies.
The higher the bounty, the more materials you can redeem.
So that’s it
You guys go trade
We have to leave beforehand
Goodbye
Thank you, goodbye
It’s reward order No. 37
You can exchange it for food and weapons
Water, water, I want water
This is how it turns out to be exchanged
Wolffy, let’s go redeem it as well.
You can redeem food, weapons and water
water we need water
It takes three robbers to exchange for a bottle of water
That’s outrageous!
They’re obviously outsiders. The low reward
is just because the robbers you caught were too weak.
Are there any rewards for more water?
Of course there are
The highest reward currently is
The robber known as Blue Scarf
So far no one has been able to catch them
why
Their whereabouts are mysterious
All I know is that they are very powerful.
Are there any tasks that are simpler and more rewarding?
Then choose this one
She looks like Tibbie
What did she do that warrants such a high reward?
she is lost
Her father is eager to find his daughter
and set a generous reward
So that’s it
Why did you drink our water?
Information is a commodity. That’s the rule here.
Yeah. Any questions?
No, no, no
The world is really dangerous
The water we finally exchanged for it was just gone.
We need to find rifts in the desert
But the orders we can do are far too meager.
If only a wanted person could just come to me on their own!
Quickly, if you catch her, you can change the water.
she is Tib—
No matter if she looks like Tibbie, take her back
Otherwise, she would be captured by other bad guys while running around.
you’re right
hello
doll
no
let me go
don’t be afraid
We don’t mean any harm
Your dad is looking for you. We’re just here to take you home.
He is not my father
They were just talking nonsense to catch me.
I won’t go with you
Miss, when will you get rid of your habit of lying?
It’s you
Meet again
What is your relationship with her?
I’m her dad’s driver
In addition to transporting supplies on weekdays,
I help find traces of Miss Xiao Mei
If it weren’t for the kindness of you two, I wouldn’t be able to catch her today.
lie
you bad guys
let me go
Wolffy, do you think he looks familiar?
Aren’t you a robber on the reward order?
To be continued